how's it going everyone Timbers 1:05
here with a very special video today I
decided to make it up to view of this
week's event and I gotta tell you this
week's [ __ ] suck yeah I'm not kidding
[ __ ] [ __ ] get this Microsoft just know
now and this pain in 2018 and there's
pain will stop coming with computers why
are you [ __ ] kidding me no I'm not
making this [ __ ] up
go ahead downing 2018 and this paint
will be tooken off computer new ones
because they don't think people use it
anymore because I have no purpose that's
[ __ ]
are you [ __ ] kidding me
one look at my any channel who is not
using that [ __ ] I'm using that [ __ ]
are you [ __ ] kidding me oh my God I
mean it just just a few days ago the
lead of Leah's house [ __ ] God are you
[ __ ] kidding me are you
cuz this we daddy was I mean what's
gonna happen next is you lil walking a
lot [ __ ] down some [ __ ] is to be
locking our poop himself oh my God
I mean can you not see people use NMS
page why don't think your dog has some
[ __ ] God
all in the same week hotel many linkin
park songs on my TV channel
[Music]
Dave my go-to bears my videos are you
[ __ ] kidding me because this weekend
you was I don't think so
I don't [ __ ] think so God damn
oh my God
you know what you know what the problem
with this is this is just another
stepping stone I have to [ __ ] walk
past to make my videos when I want to
make a video
I gotta go download something eh
des des des is crap
are you kidding me oh you serious right
now
oh my [ __ ] God I can't believe this
you can't believe this what the [ __ ] are
you serious right now just taking away
any paint I use that [ __ ] I use that
big every day seriously but what do you
expect me to use other than that it's my
scoff can we do this really can't do
this this is just making me work harder
proposing oh I'm tired of it [ __ ]
by the way about Lincoln Park I make
your memorial video and should be up in
a few days now right now because after
hearing this info I got a wait time
Edition now really I mean does not only
probably more video was gonna be out
today but he can now because all this
everything [ __ ] to malecon a waste time
contact marks off Aspen [ __ ] dog take
you down are you serious peace out
[ __ ] out I don't God deal with this
right now
I got take a [ __ ]